goddessinthehouse.com 2018-08-31

# | Diaries of a Domestic Goddess

_If you have any questions at all about what is outlined in this Privacy Policy, please contact me at LeahDGoddess@gmail.com and I will respond in a timely fashion._

Here at Diaries of a Domestic Goddess your privacy is very important.  This police has been developed in order for you to understand how data is collected, how it is used, and how (if any) communication is made.

Like a lot of Web sites, Diaries of a Domestic Goddess uses “cookies” and Web server logs to collect information about how the site is used.  Information collected may include date and time of individual visits, pages viewed, time spent on the Web site, the site last visited, your IP address, and email address (if entered).

**Cookies:**  When you visit most websites, a “cookie is placed in a part of your hard drive to allow that website to know and record your preferences in regards to that site.  On Diaries of a Domestic Goddess, we use Stat Counter to collect our stats.  While the stat collecting program may change, all collect cookies.

**IP Addresses:**  Every time you connect to the internet, your computer uses an IP address.  Your IP address is how your computer is identified.  IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server and Stat Counter as “traffic data”.

**Email Addresses:**  Your email address is ONLY collected if YOU enter it.  You may enter it if you wish to subscribe to the RSS feed for Diaries of a Domestic Goddess.  Another place you may be asked to enter your email address is when you are leaving a comment.  Your email addresses are never sold or used for any purpose other than to send you the RSS feed or contact you in the event that you win a contest on Diaries of a Domestic Goddess.

**Ad Servers:**  Diaries of a Domestic Goddess has relationships with other companies and allows them to place ads on our site.  The ad servers may collect certain information from your visit.  The information collected may include your IP address, domain type, and clickstream activity.  Please check out their sites for their Privacy Policy.  Diaries of a Domestic Goddess uses Google Adsense.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

_Diaries of a Domestic Goddess reserves the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.  If this policy changes, please understand that in no way will the personal information submitted or collected will not be used that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy._
